( Watch on kissasia.biz or asiankh.org )
[mysterious music playing]
[thunder crashes]
[quiet chatter]
[Max] We all know how this is gonna end.
So let's just cut to the fun part where you say yes.
[Sara] The lady doesn't lie.
Against your will, you're gonna have a good time.
You did not confirm.
-The boat you book... it's gone. -[laughter nearby]
Hmm. Right. But you do have other boats.
[James] Just tell us how much more.
[laughter]
[squeals]
Babe, could you please get Adrienne and Greg out of here?
Yeah. Yeah.
-Hey. Let's go. -What?
-Go sit down. -What?
[♪ courtship. sings "Warm Waters"]
I'm sorry about them.
Listen, I promise you're gonna have a blast with us.
Maybe that bigger boat is available, huh?
I would love to see you on the bridge of that bad boy.
-[Adrienne] Come here, cutie. -[Greg] Mm.
[muttering]
[Adrienne] Mm. Mm.
[Greg] Mm.
-Are you seeing this? -Wow.
[yawning]
Relax, James, it's Thailand.
No one cares about PDA.
Yeah, man. Hey.
Sorry your lady castrated you back there.
Castration's a big word, new guy.
-Phi Beta Kappa, bro. -[clears throat] At ASU.
[laughs] Okay. Guys, wh-why don't we just get some beers and go to the beach?
Give it a second, Greg.
You clearly don't know about the Max magic.
[laughs, whoops] She's so funny.
[laughs] Okay, come.
-[clears throat] Boat this way. -[Sara] Yeah.
Maximum effect!
-Max, you're amazing. -[Max] Thank you.
[James] Well done.
No reservation, no deposit, no problem?
Oh, you know I'm allergic to logistics.
[gasps] Hi, little guy. Hi.
Hi, little guy.
-[monkey screeches] -[screams]
Little monster.
Oh, he's not so bad.
-[hisses viciously] -[gasps]
[sighs]
-Hey, hold up! -♪ Do-do-do-do-do-do ♪
[♪ Jared Lee & Ace Hood sing "Livin' the Life"]
♪ Do-do-do-do-do Do-do-do-do-do-do ♪
♪ Livin' the life ♪
♪ Every day and night, we're livin' the life ♪
-♪ Hands up to the sky ♪ -[whooping]
♪ We're doing it right ♪
♪ Feelin' like a billion dollars with you by my side ♪
♪ Every day and night, every day and night, like ♪
♪ Do-do-do-do-do-do ♪
-[coughing] -♪ Do-do-do-do-do ♪
♪ Hey ♪
-[camera clicking] -♪ Do-do-do-do-do-do ♪
♪ Livin' the life ♪
♪ Do-do-do-do-do-do ♪
♪ Do-do-do-do-do ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Do-do-do-do-do-do ♪
♪ Livin' the life ♪
♪ More life, more drinks, more vibes ♪
♪ Sexy, she just my type ♪
♪ Money, throw it up in the sky ♪
♪ One life, you can't do this twice ♪
♪ Why not live it up, I'm rich ♪
♪ I work too hard for the days like this ♪
♪ Right now I'm way too lit ♪
-[screams] -♪ And the view so nice ♪
-♪ I ain't worried 'bout-- Shh ♪ -♪ No matter what we do, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ all of our dreams are coming true, ooh, ooh ♪
[camera clicking]
♪ No matter what we do, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ all of our dreams are coming true, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Livin' the life ♪
♪ Oh, yeah, we livin' ♪
♪ Oh, oh, yeah, we livin' ♪
♪ Livin' the life ♪
-♪ Oh, yeah, we livin' ♪ -[laughing]
♪ Oh, oh, yeah, we livin' ♪
♪ Oh, yeah, we livin' ♪
♪ Livin' the life ♪
[song ends]
[Max] It's a once-in-a-lifetime thing.
[Sara] But is it, like, a real job?
[Max] Yes, with Sabrina Carpenter's swimwear line.
Her investment guy knows my dad from Yale.
I'm gonna be running their socials, and in, like...
Two years, I'm gonna be running the whole thing.
[both laughing]
But do you even like Sabrina Carpenter?
I mean, I like having fun.
[♪ GALCHANIE sings "Taboo (ft. Tobii)"]
What are you thinking?
I mean, it's cool, but...
We've been talking about New York all year.
That was the deal, and now it's changed.
You're going to L.A. It changes everything.
I'm living in the moment,
I'm taking advantage of an opportunity, and you are coming with me.
I just accepted that job.
You know, the one I worked really hard to get.
I can't just bail.
You're not bailing.
You're pivoting.
-You're so funny. -[Max laughing]
[both laughing]
I mean...
What would I do for work?
Where would I live?
-I-I don't know anyone in L.A. -You'll know me.
That's all you need to know.
You and me, till the stars burn out.
Ugh, all right. No more New York, L.A. talk.
Can we just swim?
I got to school these amateurs in flip cup, but you go.
[Sara] By myself?
[Max] Hey, yo, Adrienne, you're on my team!
-[Adrienne] Okay. -New York's over. Trust me.
♪ Drive me crazy, I ain't even got no whip ♪
-[song ends] -[playful screaming]
[♪ Disco Lines & Tinashe sing "No Broke Boys"]
-[Greg] Oh! That's the stuff! -[laughter]
[playful shouting in distance]
[burbling]
♪ No broke boys, no new friends...
-[Greg laughing] -Oh, God, I'm gonna kill you!
Hey, um, go for me. I have to pee.
[Max] Okay. Mm.
-[Greg] Oh, yeah. -[Max] Mm, mm.
♪ No broke boys, no new friends ♪
♪ I'm that pressure, give me my tens ♪
♪ Ain't no lie, ain't no shade ♪
♪ Fuck on me...
-[Max laughing] No! -Hey.
We go back now.
Where other girl?
Uh, she's in the bathroom.
♪ Fuck on me, then you know he paid...
-Yeah, there we go! -[screams] Go to hell, Greg.
-Oh. -I call re--
[engine revving]
[Greg and Max shouting playfully]
Hey! Come back!
Hey! I'm still in here! Oh, my God!
-♪ I'm that pressure, give me my tens ♪ -[indistinct chatter]
-♪ Ain't no lie, ain't no shade... -Hey!
-[Greg] Oh! -[Max] Greg, Greg, Greg, Greg, Greg.
[Sara] Hey!
Hey!
-Guys, I'm still here! -[playful shouting in distance]
Oh, my God.
Unbelievable.
-[gasps] -[suspenseful music playing]
[short, gasping breaths]
Ow. Ow.
[groaning]
[pained groaning]
[screaming] Oh, God!
[groaning]
[shouting]
[shouting frantically]
[pained whimpering, sobbing]
Oh, my God! Get off me!
[gasping]
[screams]
[pained grunting]
[lively chatter, whooping]
Hey, uh, where's Sara?
[groans] What?
Where the hell is Sara?
Hey, hey, hey, hey! Stop the boat!
[Sara groaning, hissing]
Babe, I am so sorry. We didn't know.
[Sara groaning]
Damn, how many were there?
[breathing sharply]
All of them.
Yeah, it's pretty typical for Thailand.
[Sara breathing heavily]
You guys left me.
[Adrienne] I-I didn't know you were in the water.
I-I didn't know we were moving.
I mean, I guess I knew, but I was confused
-'cause the captain asked me-- -[Sara groans]
[Sara] Jesus, Greg, just-- Thank you.
-Stop. -Just stop a second.
But you're-you're... you're gonna be okay.
Thank God. Right?
So, you're gonna be okay. I'll take care of you.
-Um, let's just go. It-it's getting late. -[Sara groaning]
[Adrienne] We're sorry.
[♪ neek sings "I'll Choose U (Ibiza Remix)"]
-[Max gasps] -[Greg] Thank you.
[James] Wow.
Well, dig in, everybody.
[James] All right.
[Greg and Adrienne chuckling]
♪ You're still on my mind ♪
♪ After all this time...
God, I am just so pissed.
I-I'm gonna drag that boat guy on Yelp.
It was no one's fault. It just happened.
Leaving someone behind is, like, a pretty crazy thing to just happen.
Right? I mean, it's, like, basic safety.
Like, do a head count. It feels like it's captaining 101.
You know, Sara, if you want, I can totally have my dad, like, sue his ass
Or at least, like, send him a letter and freak him out.
-I don't blame him. -[Max] Okay.
Yeah. Yeah, you're probably right.
Um, it was probably just one of those horrible things
Where everything lined up wrong.
You know, like, like, we were partying and-and you were off somewhere, and--
L-Like I said, like I said, it was no one's fault.
Except for whoever invented Jägermeister.
-[laughter] -[Adrienne] Yeah, right?
Can we Yelp-review Jägermeister?
-That's a good idea, babe. -Yeah, thank you.
I-I totally lost track of time. I thought you were on the boat, Sara.
But I wasn't.
Yeah, but I'm not in charge of everything,
-like, every last detail. -Since when?
[sighs]
Have a great dinner, guys.
I just wanted to have a fun dinner.
So then stay, have a fun dinner.
Yeah, like that's actually an option.
So it's like, I know we left you for dead out in the open waters
And now you're covered in welts, but let's not forget the real victim here: Max.
Listen, you guys have been joined at the hip since sophomore year.
I don't know, I-I think maybe a little L.A., New York distance
Could be a really good thing.
[chuckles]
L.A.'s not so bad, right?
I like strip malls.
Or go to New York.
Just blaze your own trail.
-I'm sorry I didn't take care of you. -I'm sorry for making such a big deal.
-I'm sorr-- I'm actual-- I-I am sorry. -[Sara] I'm sorry. [laughs]
Thank you.
-Well, I'm sorry I had to pee. -[Sara] I'm sorry about that, too.
Let's be honest, it's not the first time
Adrienne's tiny bladder has caused absolute mayhem.
-Oh, wow. -You don't know the half of it.
That.
[mysterious music playing]
[Greg] Oh!
-[Greg and James hollering] -[Sara, Max and Adrienne laughing]
Greg's basically a yellow Lab, right?
Or is he a golden retriever?
You know he was holding both on Bumble?
-[Max groans] -Ew.
-I know, I know. -[laughter]
We're glad that you brought him.
Yeah, he checks the box... for now.
[Greg and James laughing, chattering indistinctly]
[Max] Do you think our boyfriends are about to kiss?
[Sara] They look like they're gonna kiss.
[Adrienne] I'm gonna go get
-a front-row seat for that. -Ooh.
-Yeah. -Yep!
-Get it. -Go get it.
-Mm-hmm, mm-hmm. -Get 'em.
Hey, I really am sorry about today.
It's cool. We're good.
No, I'm trying to be accountable here.
I-I know that I have a bad habit of...
Charging ahead.
It's not just you.
I've been kind of weird this week, too.
Your dad.
-Yeah. -Yeah.
I know it's just that one backpacking trip he took here,
But I keep wanting to send him a picture...
[melancholy music playing]
...or ask him what his favorite beach was or what kind of street food he ate.
Just want to talk to him.
We-we don't have to do the caves tomorrow if it's too much.
No.
That's the one thing I do know.
He loved swimming in those caves.
Tomorrow, Devil's Mouth.
For your dad... and for all of us.
[chuckles]
You know, if you hadn't have charged ahead when he died,
I probably would've left school.
[Max] Mm.
You basically wouldn't let me give up.
Well, trauma sees trauma.
-Dead Parents Society and all that. -Yeah, yeah.
Dragging me to those parties.
Yeah. Questionable outfits.
[both] Why were we always matching?
Always matching. [laughs]
Okay, the point is you saved me.
It's real.
Max magic.
-Come on, say it. -No.
Say it.
-Only if you leave me alone. -Never.
You and me...
Till the stars burn out.
Yes! Yes! That a girl.
-[Max laughs] -[Adrienne squeals]
-Come on, skinny-dipping! [squeals] -Skin-- Oh!
-Hell yeah. Hell yeah. -[Adrienne squeals]
Oh, my God.
-Come on. -No, no, I'm good.
I'm good here.
Oh, shit. Sorry.
Uh... you know what?
Never mind. You know what? They can do it.
-Uh, but let-- -No. Seriously.
James and Greg can be naked together.
It's what they want.
You guys go, please. I'm gonna be upset if you don't go, okay?
Just go have fun.
-Go, go, go, go, go, go! -[Adrienne] Okay!
[Max and Adrienne whooping]
[Adrienne] Skinny-dipping!
[whooping, shouting]
-[James] Hustle, hustle, hustle. -[Greg] Let's go, man. Hustle over here.
[James] Take it off, take it off.
-Get over here! -[Greg] Let's go, babe!
[plaintive music playing]
[squealing, laughter]
Whoo!
[grunting]
[leaves rustling in wind]
-[Max screaming] -[James] What? What?
What? What? What was it?
I-I felt something. I felt... I felt something.
-Oh, my God! I felt something! -[jarring, intense music playing]
Go! Go!
[panting]
What--
No, no, I-I felt something. I felt something.
-What was it? -[Max stammers]
There, there, there. What's that?
The thing that just rolled up on the beach, washed up.
[tense music playing]
[James] Whoa.
[Adrienne] Is that a bite?
Okay, this is the opposite of fun. Okay, so delete, delete, delete.
Let's-let's just go back, and the van picks us up at 9:00 a.m.
Eight, babe.
Okay, I said 8:00.
Okay, it's freshwater stuff only tomorrow.
It's nothing to be scared about.
Come on, Sara. It's okay.
[rousing music playing]
♪ ♪
[James] Wow.
This is insane.
[Adrienne] Oh, cool. Is that it?
-What? -The Devil's Mouth.
You see how the teeth are, like, reflecting in the water?
[Sara] Not yet.
And if it's anything like the photos online, it's way more impressive.
And way far away.
Sh-Should we have packed more snacks?
I bet Sara has a protein bar in that backpack.
-You bet I do. -[laughter]
Don't come for me if you need snacks or emergency supplies.
Okay? And I promise you guys, Devil's Mouth is gonna be worth the wait.
And yes, this is also waterproof.
Oh, you think of everything.
Yeah, blame my Boy Scout brothers.
Always be prepared.
[camera clicks]
Cute.
♪ ♪
-[Adrienne] Hello. -Hello.
Hi!
There he is.
[speaks Thai]
My name is Wat. I will be your cave guide today.
So, has anyone been in caves before?
No?
We're all cave virgins. Nice.
And does anyone have fear of water or of swimming?
I'm not afraid of the water, just what might be in it.
[Wat] Don't worry.
Uh, water is never more than ten, 15 meters deep.
And maybe some small fish, like Finding Nemo.
-[gasps] That's my comfort movie. -That's my comfort movie.
[quiet, indistinct chatter]
I'll be fine.
Just keep swimming.
Well, we swim later. Now we kayak, okay?
[grunting] Okay. Okay.
-All right. -Whoa.
[rousing music playing]
[whooping]
[Max] Oh, my God!
[laughter]
Wow.
[whooping]
[chuckles] My mom is gonna love these.
Greg, you mention your mom one more time...
-[imitates cat growling] -[chuckles]
[laughing]
-[whooping] -[James] Yeah!
[whooping]
[Greg] Very nice! Very nice!
[Max] So this is it?
-This is cave entrance. -Oh.
Not Devil's Mouth.
It coming.
-Look at that. -[Sara groans]
[Sara hisses in pain]
-You okay? -Yeah.
Okay. All right.
-[camera clicks] -[laughter]
-Cute. -Super.
[Adrienne] If you go into a cave and you don't make a TikTok about it,
Did it even happen?
-It happened. -Um, hey.
Handsome diver, four o'clock.
[quiet chatter]
[Wat] Okay, guys.
If you have any problems, please do not panic.
-Just come tell me. -[James groans]
-Sorry. -Ow.
So, today, we are going to take this Green Path here,
Like you requested, Sara. Easy.
Oh, but this looks cool, though.
Maybe we try the Red Path.
[chuckles] No, no, no.
Uh, early monsoon already flood Red Path.
Better for scuba.
Thought monsoon season didn't start for another month, right?
We had worst storm just a few days ago.
But everything beautiful now, right?
[Max clearing throat]
Uh, I heard that the Red Path is also pretty cool.
-Yeah, personally, I'm a big fan of red. -[Adrienne] Yeah, you are, baby.
Okay, well, I read that the Green Path is just as cool and it's slightly easier.
Yes, uh, Red Path is too hard.
Too hard? Oh, my God, then we must.
Hello.
-I'm Max. [kisses] -Hi.
-Nice to meet you. [kisses] -Okay.
I'm the CEO of fun, so let's have a little fun, shall we?
[Wat] Uh... uh...
[chuckles] Uh...
O-Okay. [laughs] Sounds good.
Um, we can take Red Path, if that's okay with you, Sara.
[chuckles softly]
Of course.
-Yeah, Sara. -[Max] Yeah.
Watch out. Redhead on the Red Path.
[Max] We so fun.
Uh, life jacket is optional, but I would say you should--
-Oh, I'll take one. -Okay.
Thank you.
-Here you go. -Thanks.
Hey. Did the, uh... did the loud one do that to you?
Like, just blink twice if you need help.
Uh... pissed off some jellyfish.
-Oh. -Mm.
I've done the whole cave system back here.
The worst thing I've ever seen is a really fat, depressed catfish.
Not pretty.
Good to know.
You know, we're lucky to get in here.
It's been closed down for a while 'cause of the storm surge.
-Oh. -Yeah, today's the last day
Before they shut down for Songkran.
Thai New Year. Right.
If you ever get scared out there, just look down, all right?
I'll wink back up at you.
See you.
Were you guys just comparing whistle brands?
-[inhales sharply] Something like that. -Ah.
-Wedding's in the fall. -Right.
-Small, intimate. -Cool.
-Scuba-themed, obviously. -Mm-hmm.
[Max] Hey, you two.
-It's now or never. -[James] Okay.
-All right. -Let's go.
I'm just gonna get my stuff together.
[mysterious music playing]
[Max and Adrienne whooping]
[whooping]
Come on.
Be like Greg. Don't think about it.
Yeah, I never think.
[whooping]
No jellyfish. I promise.
[chuckling]
-[tense music playing] -[screams]
Whoa, what is it? What's the matter? What is it? What's wrong?
-[breathing heavily] -[Wat] Sara, you okay?
An eel.
Eels in ocean, not in cave.
I saw it. I definitely saw it.
Many things look like eel.
[Greg laughing loudly]
Greg, babe, please, no.
-[laughing] 'Cause, you know-- -[James] Uh, don't. Don't finish it.
Don't even finish the sentence.
[faint, indistinct chatter]
[James] No turning back now.
[mysterious music playing]
[quiet, indistinct chatter]
[burbling]
[Wat] Next cave down Red Path is very special.
You will see.
But no noise.
It is the Devil's Mouth.
Pretty sure "the Devil's Mouth" is what the lacrosse team called Adrienne.
Oh, you're just jealous.
[Wat] Sara, I just wanted to tell you something.
Before you go under, full exhale, then deep breath.
Okay?
[others chattering indistinctly]
[atmospheric music playing]
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter]
[Wat] This is Blue Tunnel.
Sunlight hits white sand.
Shows us the way home.
[Max] Tunnel means exit. Got it.
[tranquil music playing]
Wow.
[Greg] This is the coolest cave ever.
Shh.
-[James] S-Sorry. -[Greg] Sorry.
-[thuds] -Ow.
Freaking Red Path.
[mysterious music playing]
[James] Whoa.
[Max] Wow.
This is Devil's Mouth.
See?
Teeth.
[bats squeaking]
[wings fluttering]
-[wings fluttering] -[screams]
[bats squeaking]
[Wat] Shh.
[quiet, indistinct chatter]
[whistles]
-[bats squeaking frantically] -[dramatic music playing]
Sara, hurry.
Kind of cool, actually.
[gasps]
Wait, Max. [grunts]
[tense music playing]
[grunts, breathes heavily]
[sighs]
Ah, Sara, you okay?
Yeah, I'm good.
This is the Skeleton Cave.
Real bones below.
Human? Animal?
-Yes. Human. -[James clears throat]
-Wat. -Yes?
-You said "human bones." -Mm-hmm.
What? Why?
These caves, they're very old.
Many, many years.
Sinkhole and boom.
Whole village die.
We are guests here.
Caves are master.
If you do not respect the caves--
James, the bone cave?
-Get it, bro? -[Wat] Hey.
-[laughing] The bone cave? -[Wat] Hey.
This is no joke.
[quiet, indistinct chatter]
[Max] You okay? It's okay.
God, James. Come on.
Human bones.
[Max] They're already dead. They're already dead.
[mysterious music playing]
-[Adrienne] Sara! We have an emergency! -[gasps]
Emergency photo op.
-[chuckling] -Come on.
[Wat] Here. I'll take for you.
[Greg] Start flexing, James.
-[quiet, indistinct chatter] -[grunts]
-[Wat] Okay, ready? -[Sara] Okay.
One, two, three.
[camera click echoes]
[Max] Great.
-Now we have Greg in our memories forever. -Yeah.
-[Adrienne] That's funny, yeah. -[Max] Uh, I want you to shoot up.
-[Adrienne] Okay. -[James] Phi Beta Kappa.
You'd think he'd understand what "respect the caves" means.
Ow. Greg, Greg!
He should really point his toes more.
-[indistinct chatter] -[Sara] Max, the director.
-Taking charge since sophomore year. -Mm-hmm.
How did we survive without her?
-[grunts] -[others scream]
Hey. What'd I tell you?
This rock very weak.
You cause collapse, we die.
Yeah, yeah, I'm sorry. It was an accident.
-I-I didn't mean to. -[snickers]
[Wat] We go now.
Next cave.
[quiet laughter]
Wh-What?
Ooh, you got yelled at.
[quiet, indistinct chatter]
[foreboding music playing]
[indistinct chatter continues]
What is that?
[James] What? What is it?
[Greg] What's that smell?
Ew.
[Wat] These are saltwater fish from the ocean.
[James] The hell?
Uh, all these fish are dead.
Baby, will you cancel our sushi plans tonight?
How did they even get in here?
[Sara] That cave opens to the ocean through that passage.
[Wat] Yes.
But the opening is very high.
Too high.
The storm could have flooded the ocean water in here.
Then the fresh water killed all the sea life.
Uh, should we turn around?
[Wat] Uh...
I take you back a different way.
We go this way. Next cave.
You okay?
You can come with me.
Yeah, I'm fine.
Hey, Wat, what's with all the special attention?
Uh, your friend, she tip extra,
Say that you need extra care.
I'm fine.
I paid for the trip, so I'm the one who tips.
No more special treatment, okay?
-Okay. Yes. -Thank you.
[others chattering indistinctly]
[burbling]
[tense music playing]
[gasps] Geez.
[exhales heavily]
[ominous music playing]
This is sick.
Whoa.
Wow.
[quiet, indistinct chatter]
-[Sara grunts] -[Max] How are the welts?
Fine. Fresh water doesn't sting as much.
-Yeah. -Is that why you put Wat on me?
What?
-He told me about your little tip. -Well, babe,
You made such a big deal about me, like, not looking out for you the other day.
I just thought--
Pay someone to infantilize me?
Sara, give me your knife.
Gonna fight to the death?
[others chattering indistinctly]
[atmospheric music playing]
-[Sara] Max. -[Max laughs]
Now it's carved in stone.
You're stuck with me. Boom!
[muffled splashing]
-Okay, cheeseball! -[Max laughing]
Gay!
-[screams] -What? What?
I felt something on my fin.
[breathing heavily]
I don't see anything.
Hey, uh, it's okay.
-Yeah. -It's good. Come on, let's go.
Hey, come on.
It's okay.
Rocks are sharp. Go slow.
It's amazing how old they are and still so fragile.
Limestone sinkhole.
-That's how the caves are formed. -[Greg] Limestone.
Carbonate sedimentary.
Let me guess: rocks for jocks?
[laughing] You know it, baby.
It's my first A.
-[James] Uh... -Minus, minus.
[Adrienne whimpers]
-Oh, damn. One of them cut me. -What's-- What--
Oh, no, no, no, no, I can't look.
Come on, come on.
Oh, I can't look. I can't look. I can't look.
There's damn knives all under us.
Are you good, Cousin Greg?
[Adrienne] Oh, oh, right. Uh, he has this thing about blood.
Uh, babe, remember the mantra?
-What's his thing about blood? -Yeah.
He can't be around it.
-"I am safe. I am special. I am me." -Yeah. Yeah. I'm me.
Oh, my God, no.
-No. -[James] Seriously, though, Greg,
-you all right, bud? -Is it... is it done?
Th-The blood, did she s-stop bleeding?
[Sara] Can you guys calm him down?
"I am safe, I am special, I am..." wh-whatever.
[Greg] Well, when I was a kid, my brother pranked me.
It was a fake bike accident with our neighbor Tanner, who was like five.
-He used ketchup as blood. -[chuckles] Classic.
Well, it totally traumatized me.
Now, whenever I'm around blood, I-I... I panic.
Now all I see is dead Tan-Tan.
[Sara] That tape should hold. Do you want to keep going?
[Wat] No, no, no, no. Policy is,
If any injury, we return, so we go back now.
Okay, well, well, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Adrienne, babe, you're fine, right?
Your concern for me is touching. It really is.
I just read that the last cave is, like, a cannot-miss, you guys.
Max, she is bleeding.
Okay. How about this?
You guys start going back, and I'm gonna go check out the cave really quick,
And I'll swim really fast and catch up with you guys.
You're gonna go check out the last cave by yourself?
-Yep. -Wat, is that even safe?
[Wat] No, no, no, not safe.
[atmospheric music playing]
[tense music playing]
-[Max] Why shouldn't I do that, right? -[Adrienne] No, no, no. Hey, hey, hey.
-What? -[Adrienne] I'm fine. I'm fine.
Let's just go to the next one... together.
Yay!
[in Thai] Better get a good tip for this shit.
[in English] Wh-What'd he say?
All right, um, Greg. Hi, babe. Look at me.
No more blood. Everything is okay.
I am safe.
-I am special. -I am special.
[both] I am me.
Okay, you assholes. All together.
-I am safe. -[Greg] I'm safe.
[Adrienne, Max and Greg] I am special.
[Adrienne, Max, Greg and Sara] I am me.
[atmospheric music playing]
[Adrienne] Okay, this is it.
-Better be worth it. -[James] I don't see anything yet.
[Wat] Lights off.
[Max] Guys, lights off.
[James] Lights off, Greg. Lights off.
-[laughing] Oh, my-- -What?
Oh, my God.
-[whooping] -No way.
[laughter]
Whoa. What?
-[James] Whoa. -[Sara] Okay.
Looks like the CEO of fun had a point.
She is occasionally right, it's true.
-You know I can hear you guys. -[Greg] Whoa, guys.
Check it out. I'm freaking Harry Potter.
[whoops, laughs]
This is pretty epic, actually.
-Yes! Yes! -I take care of you. I always do.
[chuckling]
[laughter, whooping]
-[Greg] This is crazy. -[Wat] Okay.
-We go now. -[Max] What?
-No, we just got here. -I take you out longer way.
More caves to see.
Can we just chill here for a couple more minutes?
My leg is kind of killing me.
It-it's not bleeding, is it?
Just two more minutes, okay?
-[Greg chuckles] -[Max] Whee!
[muffled laughter]
[ominous music playing]
How's the scrape, Ade? Do you want my life vest?
You know what, actually, that would be amazing.
-Okay. -Thank you. Yeah.
[others chattering indistinctly]
Here.
Thank you.
[inhales deeply]
[tense music playing]
[muffled shout]
-[gasping] -[Adrienne] What? What? What happened?
-What happened? -[Sara] The diver, he's hurt.
-[Greg] Wh-What are you talking about? -[Adrienne] It's okay. It's okay.
-Deep breaths. Deep breaths. -There's... there's so much blood.
-You okay? -Like, bleeding?
Babe, it's okay. It's okay. Hang on. Everything's fine. Just--
-[Sara] Blood. -Okay, we need to leave now.
But shouldn't we help him? Go down and look for him or something?
I--
[gasps]
Chà-lam.
Ch-Chà-lam? What does that mean?
Wh-What does that mean? What are you saying?
-Shark. -[suspenseful music playing]
[Sara, Adrienne and Max] What?
-Shark? -In here?
[Max] Wait, what are you saying? Wait, what are you--
-What-what-what-- No. -[Adrienne] No! No, no, no, no, no!
-[Max] Sara? -[Greg] You said shark?
[Max] He said... he said... he said... you heard--
-He said shark? You heard him say shark? -Yes, he said shark.
-Just calm down. Calm down. -[overlapping chatter]
Quiet!
I don't know--
Just, like, listen to Wat.
We have to go now.
-Okay. -[Wat] Okay?
I'm sorry, how is there a shark in a freshwater cave system?
Th-There are sharks that can do fresh and salt water.
Okay, but how'd it get into a cave? Did it order a goddamn Uber?
Guys, I don't think this is something we need to figure out right now.
-Oh, I didn't call my mom today. -Look, just follow me, okay?
-[Max] How do you know it's a shark? -Are you okay?
-Okay, let's just go. -I'll be fine.
-[Wat] We have to go. -Let's just go with Wat.
Yeah, I'll go anywhere there's not blood.
-We have to go. -[Sara] Let's go with him.
-Wait. Wait, wait, wait. -Come on.
Okay, I don't want to race through the caves
If there's something dangerous out there, okay?
What is the plan?
I mean, it's a valid question.
None of us should get in the water if we don't have a plan.
I am the plan. I keep you safe. We go now.
-Yes. -[Max] No, that's a bad idea.
-No, no! -[Adrienne] Stop arguing, Max. Just--
[Greg] Wait, that doesn't make s--
-What-what if he doesn't come back? -[James] I don't think that's a bad idea.
-[Max] I'm literally not gonna follow him. -He know... he knows what he's doing.
No, forget him. I'm not going underwater.
[overlapping arguing]
Are you okay?
[Max] Why would we go with him?
-Why would we go in the water that-- -[Adrienne] Max, we--
-[Sara] Are you serious? -Okay, follow me.
-Hang on. Just one second. -I go now. Come if you want.
[overlapping arguing]
-I'm not leaving. -[arguing continues]
Wat?
-Wat? -[Max] No one is listening to me!
No one is listening to me!
-[overlapping arguing continues] -[tense music playing]
-Wat! -[arguing stops]
[Adrienne gasps]
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
Where'd he--
What?
He's gone.
[Adrienne whimpers softly]
No, no, no, no, this-this isn't... this isn't happening.
It's not happening.
I think it is.
[foreboding music playing]
[Greg] I'm gonna die.
-I'm gonna die. I'm gonna die. [mutters] -Where the hell is Wat?
Greg, buddy, you got to stop blubbering.
Max, can you just please leave him alone?
Are you sure you're okay?
Yeah, it's just the tape's a little loose.
All right, I'm gonna fix it.
I'll fix it up there when we get out of the cave, okay?
Okay, I just don't want to ask everyone to stop.
We're all getting out of here-- together.
[tense, atmospheric music playing]
Greg?
-Greg! -[Max] Shh!
Do you want it to follow us?
-Greg! -Shh!
[Greg muttering, whimpering in distance]
[James] Greg, buddy.
[Greg breathing heavily] Oh, God, I can't... I can't breathe.
I can't breathe.
Oh, my God. Oh.
Please. I'm s-- I'm sorry. Just-just-just leave me, okay?
Just-just leave me alone.
What are you talking about?
We're counting on you to Aquaman our way out of this.
-I love Jason Momoa. -Yeah.
Yeah, you do.
-Adrienne, can we borrow that life vest? -Yeah.
Time to get our superhero back in action.
Let's, uh... let's do it for Tommy, huh?
-It's Tanner. -Tanner?
-Yeah, Tanner. -Tan-Tan. Yeah.
-All right, bud. Up and over. -[Greg muttering]
Just relax. I got you.
-All right, let's go. -Oh, God.
-Let's get you out. -Oh, I... I didn't call my mom.
I-I didn't call my mom.
I should've called my mom.
[tense, atmospheric music continues]
[shuddering breaths]
[suspenseful music playing]
[screams]
[gasping breaths]
[screaming]
[Greg gasping]
[screams] Greg!
-[panicked shouting] -[head thuds]
[indistinct shouting, screaming]
[sobbing] Greg.
[frantic shouting, screaming]
[shouting and screaming stop]
[shuddering breaths]
[gasps]
[screaming]
[James] Come on, let's go!
-[Adrienne] No, we can't leave him! -We have to go.
-[James] Let's go! -[Adrienne] No, we can't leave him!
No!
[sobbing] No!
[intense music playing]
Come on.
[heavy breathing, whimpering]
James?
-[Max] Come on. Go, go! -[James] Go, go. Sara, go.
[Max] Come on, come on, come on, come on!
[James] Come on, come on. Go, go, go.
[frantic, indistinct chatter]
[pained grunting]
[Max] Okay. I'll push.
[yells]
[all breathing heavily]
[Sara] Hey, hey, hey.
Look, they're not even that bad, okay?
-Hey, it's okay. Shh. -[gasping breaths]
They're not even that deep. It's just...
We're gonna just wait for the bleeding to stop,
-and then we're gonna take you up. -No, no.
Sharks can smell a drop of blood in the ocean. It's not gonna work.
How did she get so beat up like this? I--
The rocks, when she went under. It must have dragged her.
[James stammering]
So... so what do we do?
We're gonna tape her up, okay?
And then we'll get out of here.
I-I can figure this out. I can. Just, like, let me think.
Like, no one move, no one do anything crazy.
-[shushing] -What? What?
Bull shark.
It has to be. That's what I was saying.
They can do fresh and salt water.
And they're aggressive as hell.
They-they bash their prey with their head.
-They go after you and after you. -[Adrienne laughing]
[laughing] It's like a cartoon.
It's like a guy wearing a fin hat on his...
[sobbing] ...on his head.
Oh, my God, Greg.
He calls his mom every night.
[continues sobbing]
I-I... I don't understand how this happened, okay?
This wasn't supposed to happen. This isn't supposed to--
[James] It's-it's like it's-it's... it's stuck in this maze,
And it's territorial and...
[Sara] It's gone.
[Max] I can't believe Wat left us.
We weren't listening to him.
Yeah, yeah, but he was in charge.
Which is why we should've listened to him.
Okay, well, Wat is faster than us.
So he's gonna get out of here, and he's gonna send for help.
And-and we have... we have to stay here,
-and we're gonna wait. -Oh, God.
It's the right thing to do. Okay?
It's like when you're a kid and you get lost.
You just stay where you are, and you wait and...
Wh-What are you looking at?
I'm trying to see where he might have gone.
The dead fish cave is next, then there's the bat cave.
-[Max] No. -And then we're so close.
He could've gone this way.
It's kind of like a honeycomb.
They're super narrow tunnels, so maybe the shark couldn't follow.
Oh, babe, it's a waste of time.
What do you mean?
Wat is gonna send for help, okay?
It's as easy as that.
What if he doesn't make it?
Well, someone is gonna come for us.
I... I promise.
[water dripping]
[taking deep breaths]
[burbling]
[tense music playing]
[yells]
[gasping]
[intense music playing]
-[grunts] -[splashes]
[music stops]
[gasping breaths]
-[grunts] -[jarring, intense music playing]
[screaming]
[Max] No.
No. No.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
[sobbing] No! No.
-Oh, my God. -[Max] No.
No one's coming for us.
What-what-what... what do we do? What do we do?
We figure out which of the two paths Wat took, and then we take the other one.
-No, that's impossible. -Wait, wait. There is another way.
We can get to the ocean in the next cave.
-The ocean? -Yes, I saw the passage
That leads to the hatch that opens to the sea.
-Look. It's the shortest way. -[Max] Okay, just wait, wait, wait, wait,
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
We have a map to the caves.
We do not have a map to the ocean, okay, so-- [stammers]
W-We don't know where it's gonna spit us out in the ocean.
There's a reason that the shark is stuck in here.
No.
-Adrienne. -[Adrienne whimpering] No.
You're hurt and you're bleeding, and we have to
-get you help. -No, Max, don't leave me.
-You have to stay up here. -I'm not like you.
No, Adrienne, that's what I'm saying.
[sobbing] No, Greg is dead! He's dead, and you're all just...
You're all just arguing, and he's gone.
-I don't want to die here alone. -[James] Okay.
Okay. Okay. Why don't we all just wait here?
When someone realizes
-Wat hasn't come back, we-- -[Max] It's a holiday.
We're not gonna post up here and just wait for no one, James.
I can stay with her, and... and you guys just go.
No. I don't like any of this.
We have to face the facts.
Wat did this for a living, and he's dead, okay?
So the three of us, we have to stick together
So we can get help for Adrienne.
[sniffling]
I can't leave her.
Fine.
Then give me the map, because James and I are going.
I don't think we should leave her, either.
James.
No, there's got to be a way that we can get help
Without leaving one of our friends alone and bleeding.
Then you two stay with her, but give me the map
So I can save your asses.
No.
-No. No, Max. No, please don't. -Sara, Sara, give me the map.
-Okay. -No, don't. No, no, no, no, no!
Give it to me! Give it to me!
-[screaming] -Adrienne!
-Get out of the water! Come on! -[gasping]
Get out of the water! Come on!
[gasping, coughing]
-Pull me up. Pull me up. -Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry.
-Pull me up. Pull me up. -[tense music playing]
Help!
Pull me up! Pull me up!
Adrienne, hurry up!
-[James] Reach. Reach. -[Adrienne] Okay, help me! Help me!
-[sobbing] Help. -[James] Adrienne, grab my hand!
[Adrienne] Pull me up. Pull me up.
Come on, come on, come on. Adrienne, reach! Grab my hand.
-[Sara] Come on, come on. -[James] Come on, come on.
-[Adrienne screams] -[thudding]
[screaming, whimpering]
[James] Oh, God!
It's stuck! It's stuck!
If it can't swim forward, it can't breathe.
Yeah, and it can't swim backwards.
Ade, listen, I think we can go, but we've got to go right now.
-No. -[James] Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Adrienne, we will help you.
-Okay, but we got to go right now, though. -Hey, hey, hey. Listen to me.
I'll carry you the whole way, but you got to get back in the water.
-[Max] Come on, let's go! -[Sara] I'll count us in. Let's go.
-[Max] One at a time. One at a time. -[shouts frantically, screams]
-[screams] -[James] No, Adrienne!
[intense music playing]
[Sara] All right, I'm-I'm coming.
I'm coming!
Get closer.
I can't reach.
Adrienne.
Can you grab my hand?
-Adrienne. -[Max] Look. Look.
No.
[James] Swim!
-[screams] -[Sara] Hurry up!
-Adrienne! Grab my hand! -Come on!
[James] Grab my hand!
-[screaming] -Grab it!
[screaming]
[screaming stops]
[heavy, shuddering breaths]
[voice shaking] This is so messed up.
I... I can't...
[voice shaking] How did-- She-she-she-she was--
Gone.
[somber music playing]
[sobbing]
[whimpers]
[grunts]
[whimpering]
I've never seen anyone die before.
Now I've seen two. [sniffles]
We could've saved her.
You would've died, too.
We need to get out of here. This ledge is crumbling.
-[Max whimpering] -The ocean outlet.
The honeycomb caves.
We have to go where it can't follow us easily.
So maybe it'll get stuck again. Maybe it'll die.
So the narrower the passage, the better, so--
The less time we spend in here, the better.
And the ocean is the closest way out, away from the shark.
Do you know where the shark came from, Sara?
The ocean, okay?
And I'm willing to bet it's not the only one in there.
But I think our odds are better out there.
'Cause if we get attacked in here--
But it can't follow us in there.
-You don't know that. -[James] Hey, hey, hey.
Both of you, just chill.
Okay? We're all going together.
Honestly, I think what Sara is saying makes a lot of sense.
Why are you taking her side?
I'm not taking anyone's side.
I just want to stick together.
Are you saying I can't take care of my friends?
You always do this!
You twist things!
I'm tired of it.
Being with you is tiring.
-Max, um... -[stifled sobs]
-It's not like that. I-- -[Max clears throat]
Okay.
Then let me make this really easy for the both of you.
James, no.
Are you kidding me?
I can't let her go alone. I'm sorry.
[sighs]
You're kidding me.
[breathing heavily]
[James] Max.
James.
You're coming with me?
Of course.
[Sara] Ocean outlet's right there.
But you're right, we don't know what's on the other side, so we'll try it your way.
[panting] Okay. Thank you.
We're in the Skeleton Cave, which connects to the Honeycomb Tunnel.
Okay. Okay.
Let's do it.
Thank you for trusting me.
I mean it.
[atmospheric music playing]
[Max] Map says there's an underwater entrance here.
Okay, wait. No one panic.
I'll go check it out.
[panting quietly]
Look, I made a call back there.
We let her go off on her own, how is that any better
Than what happened to you yesterday?
Because I'm not the one who swam away.
I'm the one who got left behind.
Don't pretend like you're not part of the problem, too.
What does that mean?
You let her be in charge.
[Max breathing heavily]
[Max] It's a long breath hold,
But we can do it.
I'm safe. I'm special. I'm me.
Ladies first.
[suspenseful music playing]
♪ ♪
Where do we go from here?
The map says that this cave definitely connects to the entrance,
But the only way that I can figure it out... is through up there.
I think the shark's definitely not up there.
[grunting]
-[grunts] -[debris falling]
[gasps]
[straining]
[grunts]
[panting]
[straining]
It's narrow. Like, really narrow.
-Then we better start crawling. -Okay.
[rustling]
[grunting]
[Sara groans, pants]
I don't want to die in here.
None of us want to die, babe.
No, I mean, I can't die while I'm, like...
Dicking around in Thailand.
I can't do that to my parents.
I wasted my life.
I should've, I don't know, uh, uh, taken things more seriously
And not put off growing up until law school.
What if that's all my mom gets of me?
Being an idiot.
You're not an idiot.
Not even close.
I wasted so much time.
[Sara] We're gonna get out of here.
We just got to keep moving.
If I get out of here, I swear I'm gonna--
[screaming]
No, no, no! No, no, no!
[all breathing heavily]
No. No.
[grunts]
What is that?
[distant chirping]
Shh!
-You guys hear that? -[birds chirping]
[gentle, hopeful music playing]
Can you turn your light off for a sec?
[chirping continues]
[Max] Is-is that...
[laughing] Is that daylight?
Oh, my God. Oh, my God, go, go, go!
Let's get the hell out of here! Oh, my God.
[screams]
[James yells]
[pained grunt]
What do I do? What's underneath me?
-Hold on to Sara's hand. -No, I can't. She's gonna drop me.
Stop.
[tense music playing]
Don't move.
[trembling breaths]
[whimpering]
[gasps]
-[gasping, whimpering] -[rocks splashing]
No.
[whimpering]
[Sara] James, stop. It's gonna break.
[Max continues whimpering]
-It's gone. -[Max yells]
Okay, get her up, get her up, get her up!
-I can't reach. Pull her up. -[Sara] I can't. I can't.
[grunts]
-I can't. I can't. -Help. Help me.
[straining]
-[yelps] -[Max screams]
-[sharp, heavy breathing] -I have to let you go.
No. No, babe, no, no!
-We're coming with you. -[screams]
[atmospheric music playing]
[birds chirping in distance]
[breathing heavily]
We got to go. We got to go.
Okay, hold on.
Let me just check. Let me look.
Okay? One second. [inhales deeply]
[panting]
Okay.
There's a tunnel down here.
And it has an air pocket, and I can see it,
But then we have to hold our breath and swim to the air pocket.
Do you think we can do it?
There's no other choice.
We can do it.
All right.
[tense, atmospheric music playing]
[gasping]
That felt like... like a long breath hold.
There's not a lot of air in here.
Try not to talk so much.
I'm gonna swim ahead, see how far it goes.
[inhales deeply]
-Max. -Hmm?
If we don't--
Don't even... don't even say that.
Don't even think that, okay? W-We're gonna get out of here.
Okay, the whole tunnel has air pockets, little breaks in the ceiling.
Okay, so...
Yeah, we... we swim to the next one and the next one.
Okay? Let's do it.
-[Sara inhales deeply] -Be like the shark.
Never stop moving.
[Max takes deep breath, whimpers softly]
[inhales deeply]
[suspenseful music playing]
[groaning]
[gasping]
♪ ♪
[muffled scream]
[intense music playing]
[muffled shouting]
[breathing heavily]
Go, go, go!
[inhales deeply]
[muffled screaming]
[gasping]
-[James] No air. -[Max] Keep going.
[inhales deeply]
[atmospheric music playing]
-[jarring, intense music playing] -[muffled whimpering]
[rock rumbling]
[muffled, urgent grunting]
[breathing deeply]
[breathing heavily]
[muffled grunting]
I love you.
-[mournful music playing] -[muffled whimpering]
Keep moving.
[muffled straining]
[grunting]
[gulps]
[rapid, sharp breaths]
[sobbing] Sara!
No, James!
-No. -We have to keep moving.
No, he's... he's right there.
-We have to keep moving. We do. -No. No.
I can't. No.
You and me.
No. No! [whimpering]
-We have to keep going. -I don't want-- No, I don't want to.
We're gonna make it. We're gonna make it.
One, two...
[screams, gasps]
Jesus! Oh, my God.
-It was in here. -What? [whimpers]
-[both screaming] -[intense music playing]
Oh, my God!
[frantic whimpering, screaming]
[Max sobbing]
[hyperventilating]
We got to go. We got to go.
[inhales deeply]
[atmospheric music playing]
[gasping]
Okay, get out of the water.
[both breathing heavily]
[grunting]
[tense music playing]
[screams]
That's the Ledge Cave, where we lost Adrienne.
That's the Devil's Mouth.
[bats squeaking]
And that's the ocean outlet.
[shuddering breaths]
We're right back where we started.
[screaming]
[whimpers]
[sobbing, hyperventilating]
[burbling]
What are you doing?
I'm taking only what we need.
Are you blaming me for James?
[melancholy music playing]
[Max sobs softly]
No.
I tried to save him.
I-I was pulling, and I was pulling and pulling and--
I know. I know you did.
I loved him.
-[Max sobbing] -I loved him, too.
I know.
But we tried it your way...
...and we're back to where we started.
The exit is right there, Sara.
-[splashing nearby] -[gasps]
Shh. Stay here.
-No, Sara. -I'll check it out.
No. No.
[sobbing]
-[tense, atmospheric music playing] -[bats squeaking]
-[wings fluttering] -[squeaking continues]
[jarring, intense music playing]
[bats squeaking frantically]
[gasps]
-What are you doing? -That's the Blue Tunnel.
That's the exit.
Get back.
[tense, atmospheric music playing]
[trembling breaths]
[bats shrieking]
Freeze.
I don't want it to see you.
[bats squeaking]
[Max shudders, whimpers]
Where is it?
-[gasping] -Shh.
[Max whimpering softly]
[atmospheric music playing]
[breathing heavily]
I-I can't tell the path. It's too dark.
Okay. Turn your light on.
But just briefly, okay?
I don't want it to see us if it's still in here.
[Max breathing heavily]
[whimpers]
-What are you doing? -[gasps]
-I need to see the way. -Turn it off.
[breath trembling]
[gasping breaths]
[tense music playing]
[screaming]
-Shh! -[muffled shriek]
Don't move.
[whispers] Adrienne.
Oh, no.
[Max whimpers]
You see that spot there?
We're gonna hide in the stalagmites until it leaves.
We can't let it follow us into the tunnel.
We can't.
[tense, atmospheric music playing]
[panting]
Max, stop.
No, no. Almost there. So close.
Goddamn it.
[loud, gasping breaths]
Max!
Look!
-[intense music playing] -[screaming]
Go! Go, go!
[screaming continues]
Hey!
[Max sobbing]
[screams, sobs]
Over here!
[Max screams]
[screams]
No, no!
[sobs, screams]
[gasping]
[Sara screams]
Over here! Hey!
Hey! I'm over here!
[growling]
-Oh, my God. -We're so close.
[groans, pants]
-Can you swim? -[groans]
-We're-we're... we're trapped. -It's okay.
We go to the ocean outlet.
[voice fading] If we go now, we can make it before...
[disorienting music playing]
[muffled splash, burbling]
[atmospheric music playing]
♪ ♪
[bats squeaking]
[both grunting]
[Max] Where-where is it?
Dead, I hope.
[pained whimpering]
[panting]
We're not moving to L.A., are we?
We're still here.
And once we get out of here,
We can do whatever we want and go wherever we want,
And we will have all the time in the world...
...to figure out how to live with this.
And therapy.
[Sara chuckles softly]
New York is probably better for therapists.
Keep a lookout, okay?
[Max] Mm-hmm.
Okay.
[tense music playing]
[yells]
[panting]
[strains, yells]
[breathing heavily]
[pained grunt]
[yells]
[grunts]
[gasping breaths]
[Sara whimpering, panting]
[birds chirping]
[calm, hopeful music playing]
[ominous music playing]
Damn.
[gentle music playing]
-What? -It's just all rocks down below.
[voice shaking] So it-it's over?
You-you can't just, like, climb down, like, w-with-with your rope?
It's not long enough.
It's so...
[sobbing] Oh, my God.
You-you said... you said this was gonna work.
-You said this was gonna work. -Shh. It's okay, it's okay.
Let me just think a second. It's...
It's low tide, so if we just wait for the tide to come in, and then we can...
Climb out in a few hours.
Right.
[takes deep breath]
-I'll go alone, and hopefully, the... -[Max sobs]
...water is high enough for me to jump.
What if it isn't?
Then I...
Break my legs and drown and you die by shark, Max.
I don't know.
This'll work.
This is our best shot.
[birds chirping in distance]
[ominous music playing]
[hissing growl]
[atmospheric music playing]
[hopeful music playing]
[grunts softly]
[Max] Sara!
You'll send help, right?
And I know that we've been through hell, but it's not my fault.
None of it's my fault.
God! Don't leave me down here.
[tense music playing]
What are you doing? This isn't you!
People change.
[inhales sharply]
[sobbing]
Hey.
It's okay. It's just another hour or so.
What is it?
[sniffles]
What?
I'm gonna die alone down here.
I know it.
[soft, mournful music playing]
[sobbing]
Hey.
You and me.
Till the stars burn out, right?
[sniffles]
But you're gonna have to do something
That neither one of us has ever done before.
Swim with a broken hand?
No.
Trust me.
[waves rumbling]
I can hear the waves crashing closer.
So you'll-you'll send help?
-Of course I will. -Sara, wait.
My whole life, I thought I had to be the strong one.
For my dad, for my friends.
I thought I had to carry that weight.
But I never saw you.
How strong you were.
And I'm so sorry.
I am so...
[crying] I am so very sorry.
I'm coming back for you.
[quiet, tense music playing]
-[grunting] -[waves crashing]
[panting]
[determined music playing]
Wait!
Please!
What? What are you doing?
Get back to the rock!
I-I'm coming with you.
You can't. Your hand.
I'll come back for you.
[grunts]
I can do this, Max.
Please, don't leave me.
[sighs, sniffles]
Can you get up here?
[grunting]
[yelps]
[gasping]
[Sara] Okay, hold on.
[panicked whimpering, gasping]
Help. [whimpers]
Go, grab the rope.
Just tie it around your waist and knot it.
As tight as you can.
[waves crashing]
[dramatic music playing]
[exhales sharply]
[Max whimpers]
-Okay. -Ready?
[panting] Yeah.
Start climbing.
[pained grunting]
[whimpers]
[panting] Okay.
Okay. Okay. [whimpers]
[screams]
My feet keep slipping!
All right.
Try again.
[whimpering]
[panting] Okay.
[groans]
Okay.
[panting] Okay.
[whimpers, groans]
[straining]
Okay. [grunts]
We're doing it, Sara! We're doing it!
[gasps]
[screaming]
[yelps]
[yells]
[muffled shouting]
[tense music playing]
[yelps]
[gasping]
[shudders] Max.
[whimpers]
[grunting]
[breathing heavily]
[somber music playing]
[groaning]
[panting]
"Respect the caves."
This is the Skeleton Cave.
We are guests here. Caves are master.
[Max] Sara.
Emergency photo op.
[grunting, panting]
-[Wat] This rock very weak. -[screams]
You cause collapse, we die.
[muffled splashing]
[splashing]
Hey!
Come and get it!
[splashing]
[panting]
[atmospheric music playing]
Dinnertime.
[tense music playing]
[splashing]
[intense, suspenseful music playing]
[groans]
[music fades]
[splashing]
Come on!
[intense, suspenseful music playing]
[growling]
[pained grunting]
-Come on. Get back. -[splashing]
Come back. One more time. Come back!
[shark growling]
[rumbling]
[groans]
[somber music playing]
[gasping]
[coughs]
[rapid, trembling breaths]
[hopeful music playing]
♪ ♪
[whimpers]
[birds chirping]
[panting, whimpering]
[sniffles]
[chuckles]
[laughs loudly]
[screams]
[echoing scream]
[triumphant music playing]
[music fades]
[dramatic music playing]
♪ ♪
[gentle music playing]
[music ends]